chryslercapital.com 2013-08-19

# Privacy Policy | Chrysler Capital

| 

## What does Chrysler Capital  
do with your personal information?  
  
---|---  
|   
  
## Why?

| 

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.   
  
|   
  
## What?

| 

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include: 

  * Social Security number and income 
  * Account balances and payment history 
  * Credit history and credit scores 

|   
  
## How?

| 

All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday businesses. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons Chrysler Capital chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.   
  
## Reasons we may share your personal information

| 

### Does Chrysler Capital share? *

| 

### Can you limit this sharing?  
  
---|---|---  
**For our everyday business purposes**   
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus | **Yes** | **No**  
**For our marketing purposes**   
to offer our products and services to you | **Yes** | **No**  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies** | **Yes** | **No**  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes**   
information about your transactions and experiences | **Yes** | **No**  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes**   
information about your creditworthiness | **Yes** | **Yes**  
**For our affiliates to market to you** | **Yes** | **Yes**  
**For our nonaffiliates to market to you** | **Yes** | **Yes**  
**For Chrysler Group LLC and affiliates to market to you** | **Yes** | **Yes**  
  
* Except as permitted by law, we do not share personal information in connection with the collection of a debt. 

## To limit our sharing

| 

  * Call **855-563-5635** \- our menu will prompt you through your choice(s) 
  * Visit us online: **www.chryslercapital.com** or 
  * Mail the form below 

**Please note:**   
If you are a _new_ customer, we can begin sharing your information **30 days from the date we sent this notice**. When you are _no longer_ our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice. However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.   
  
---|---  
  
## Mail-in Form  
  
---  
  
**Mark any/all you want to limit:**

  * Do not share my personal information about my creditworthiness with your affiliates for their everyday business purposes. 
  * Do not allow your affiliates to use my personal information to market to me 
  * Do not allow your affiliates to use my personal information to market their products and services to me 
  * Do not allow Chrysler Group LLC and affiliates to use personal information collected jointly by Chrysler Capital to market its products and services to me 

**Leave Blank OR** If you have a joint account, your choice(s) will apply to everyone on your account unless you mark below: 

Apply my choices only to me 

|  | Name(s) |   
---|---  
Account #(s) |   
Address  
City, Sate, Zip |   
  
THIS IS NOT A POSTCARD * MAIL THIS FORM IN A PRIVACY ENVELOPE 

Mail to: 

**Chrysler Capital**   
PO Box 961275   
Fort Worth, TX 76121-1245   
  
## What we do  
  
---  
  
**How does Chrysler Capital Inc. protect my personal information?**

| 

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.   
  
**How does Chrysler Capital collect my personal information?**

| 

We collect your personal information, for example, when you. 

  * Apply for financing or pay your bills 
  * Give us your contact information or provide employment information 
  * Give us your income information 

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies. For online banking, we or our service providers may use cookies, which are pieces of data that help web sites recognize return visitors and to personalize and enrich your online visits. For more details, please refer to our Online Privacy Policy.   
  
**Why can’t I limit all sharing?**

| 

Federal law gives you the right to limit only. 

  * Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness 
  * Affiliates from using your information to market to you 
  * Sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you 

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.   
  
**What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?**

| 

Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.   
  
## Definitions  
  
---  
  
**Affiliates**

| 

Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. 

  * Our affiliates include companies with a Santander name and financial companies such as Sovereign Bancorp 

**Nonaffiliates**

| 

Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. 

  * Nonaffiliates we share with can include banks, credit card companies, consumer finance companies, insurance companies, and direct marketing companies 

**Joint Marketing**

| 

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you. 

  * Our joint marketing partners include warranty or service contract providers, GAP insurance providers, and other insurance companies. 

## Other Important Information  
  
---  
  
**Chrysler Group LLC.:** We collect information on behalf of Chrysler Group LLC. Chrysler Group LLC will treat this information according to its privacy statement which can be accessed online at: http://www.chrysler.com/universal/privacy.html. 

**Residents of California:** Other than for our everyday business purposes, we will not share your personal information with nonaffiliates or affiliates without first giving you additional privacy choices. 

**Residents of Vermont:** Other than for our everyday business purposes, we will not share the following without first giving you additional privacy choices: (i) personal information with nonaffiliates; and (ii) personal information about your creditworthiness with affiliates or joint marketing partners. 

**Texas Residents:** Chrysler Capital is registered under the laws of the State of Texas and by state law is subject to regulatory oversight by the Office of Consumer Credit Commissioner. If you wish to file a complaint against Chrysler Capital, you should contact the Office of Consumer Credit Commissioner through one of the means indicated below: 

In Person or U.S. Mail: 2601 North Lamar Boulevard, Austin, Texas 78705-4207.   
Telephone No.: (800) 538- 1579; Fax No.: (512) 936-7610.   
E-mail: [consumer.complaints@occc.state.tx.us.](mailto:consumer.complaints@occc.state.tx.us.)   
Website: www.occc.state.tx.us.
